{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 长 x 短",
      "answer": "chang x duan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 大 x 小",
      "answer": "da x xiao"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 上 x 下",
      "answer": "shang x xia"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 高 x 矮",
      "answer": "gao x ai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 男 x 女",
      "answer": "nan x nu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 新 x 旧",
      "answer": "xin x jiu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 多 x 少",
      "answer": "duo x shao"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 教 x 学",
      "answer": "jiao x xue"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 远 x 近",
      "answer": "yuan x jin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 笑 x 哭",
      "answer": "xiao x ku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 天 x 地",
      "answer": "tian x di"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 这 x 哪",
      "answer": "zhe x na"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 前 x 后",
      "answer": "qian x hou"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 对不起",
      "answer": "dui bu qi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 没关系",
      "answer": "mei guan xi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 不客气",
      "answer": "bu ke qi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 饺子",
      "answer": "jiao zi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the meaning of 卖",
      "answer": "sell"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the meaning of 买",
      "answer": "buy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 过年",
      "answer": "guo nian"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 新年",
      "answer": "xin nian"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 新年好",
      "answer": "xin nian hao"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 新年快乐",
      "answer": "xin nian kuai le"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 祝贺",
      "answer": "zhu he"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 年糕",
      "answer": "nian gao"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 红包",
      "answer": "hong bao"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 热闹",
      "answer": "re nao"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 衣服",
      "answer": "yi fu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 橙子",
      "answer": "cheng zi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 福",
      "answer": "fu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 红色",
      "answer": "hong se"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 笔",
      "answer": "bi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 书",
      "answer": "shu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 书包",
      "answer": "shu bao"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 铅笔",
      "answer": "qian bi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 钢笔",
      "answer": "gang bi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 白板笔",
      "answer": "bai ban bi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 标记",
      "answer": "biao ji"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 橡皮",
      "answer": "xiang pi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 尺子",
      "answer": "chi zi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 磨刀器",
      "answer": "mo dao qi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 铅笔盒",
      "answer": "qian bi he"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 课",
      "answer": "ke"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 上课",
      "answer": "shang ke"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 吧",
      "answer": "ba"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 讲",
      "answer": "jiang"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 听",
      "answer": "ting"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 操场",
      "answer": "cao chang"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 动物园",
      "answer": "dong wu yuan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 进",
      "answer": "jin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 问",
      "answer": "wen"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 回答",
      "answer": "hui da"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 动物",
      "answer": "dong wu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 下课",
      "answer": "xia ke"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 来",
      "answer": "lai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 去",
      "answer": "qu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 叉子",
      "answer": "cha zi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 勺子",
      "answer": "shao zi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 筷子",
      "answer": "kuai zi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 杯子",
      "answer": "bei zi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 炒锅",
      "answer": "chao guo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 冰箱",
      "answer": "bing xiang"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 电饭锅",
      "answer": "dian fan guo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 刀",
      "answer": "dao"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 厨房",
      "answer": "chu fang"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 碗",
      "answer": "wan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 加仑水",
      "answer": "jia lun shui"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 火",
      "answer": "huo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 火",
      "answer": "huo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pinyin for 盘子",
      "answer": "pan zi"
    }
  ]
}
